as
cómo
you can imagine as I said I
os imaginaréis como ya he dicho yo he
recorded this morning that I will have it
grabado esta mañana que lo tendré ya
right away but there are so many
mismo pero hay tantos
I recorded a video about yesterday's dispute
he grabado un vídeo sobre la disputa de
about growing the blonde ok I'm not going to give my
ayer de crezco el rubio ok no voy a
opinion well giving my opinion is now because I'm going to
opinar bueno opinar es ahora porque voy
react the video takes a while some
a reaccionar el vídeo lento hace algo de
opinions will come out but basically I will give
opinión caerá pero básicamente
my opinion more extensively now in the video
opino más extensamente ahora en el vídeo
when I upload it but I would like to see since it
cuando lo suba pero me gustaría ver ya
's on the server
que está metido dentro del servidor
please what has been said so I'm
favor qué es lo que ha opinado así que
going to watch it very good morning everyone I'm a
voy a verlo muy buenos días a todos soy
trainer and welcome there hasn't been anything
formador y bienvenidos aun no ha habido
else for the channel yet ok guys it's Three
más para el canal bueno chicos soy el
Kings Day that day that I'm going to be
día de reyes ese día que voy a estar
completely out of the house but I wanted to
completamente fuera de casa pero quería
comment on what happened yesterday in the big
comentar lo que pasó ayer en el gran
okay that I think everyone has already
vale que creo que todo el mundo ya lo ha
commented on and I want to give my opinion about
comentado y quiero dar mi opinión acerca
all this which is nothing more than
de todo esto que no es nada más que una
nonsense basically I think he's
tontería básicamente que creo que está
making a mini grain of sand I
haciendo de un mini granito de arena
think he's making a damn
creo que está haciendo un maldito
desert south you know because you know because
desierto sur sabe porque sabe porque una
nonsense that is getting bigger
tontería que se está haciendo más grande
because rugby has already been
porque esto ya el rugby lo viene
dragging this for a while I said it in the
arrastrando de antes lo he dicho en el
video you will see it extensively and you
vídeo ya lo veréis extensamente y os va
will  square the other day greece made a
a cuadrar el otro día grecia le puso un
very strange comment very strange it was not
comentario muy raro muy extraño no era
a very nice comment in a video
un comentario muy agradable en un vídeo
to rubios
a rubios
okay and then the rubio is that you know
vale y entonces el rubio es que sabes
what's going on because these
qué es lo que pasa porque estos
servers I'm going to tell you what's going on
servidores os voy a decir lo que pasa
with these servers it's very
con estos servidores a mí me hace mucha
funny to me when people start saying
gracia cuando la gente se pone a decir
haha ​​on the server dallas is not there
jaja en el servidor no está dallas no
this one is not there that other one hahahahaha or
está este no está el otro jajajaja o
yesterday when they did this on
ayer cuando hicieron en el servidor este
google's server making fun of the hand they've
de google burlándose de la mano que han
made of your server which is paracetamol
hecho de tu servidor que es paracetamol
for the virus a few no what happens is
para el virus unos cuantos no que pasa
that since they invited us to the a-6 you
que como nos han invitado la a-6 usted
from another one below low budget don't
de otro debajo de bajo presupuesto no
read the welcome
lee el bienvenido
there are people who believe that the
hay gente que se cree que el servidor de
ebola server is the original and they believe that those
ébola es el original y se creen que los
who are invited there are the tops the
que están invitados ahí son los tops los
best and those who are not invited are
mejores y a los que no invitados son
[ __ ] okay no way that's not a
[__] vale no haber eso no es un
server and an event that a
servidor y un evento que haya creado una
company has created okay they take it as if
empresa vale es que se lo toman como que
youtube created that event and has
youtube ha creado ese evento y ha
chosen the crème de la crème and
elegido a la crème de la crème y al
whoever they haven't chosen is left out
quien no ha elegido se queda fuera
because you're not that good don't you  bother
porque no eres tan bueno no te molestes
no longer that is a server that
no ya eso es un servidor que han creado
two or three friends have created and they have invited the
dos o tres amigos y han invitado a la
people they get along with it's like
gente con la que se lleva bien es como
if I make a game server here
si yo hago un servidor de un juego aquí
I invite you to use and thanks well I invite ardal
invito usar y gracias pues invito ardal
to pull and play south to the turbo plan to
a halar y a jugar al sur al turbo plan a
those that I take I'm not going to invite
los que me llevo no voy a [__] invitar
jairo blogs
a jairo blogs
because jairo blog worse or better it's not that I do
porque jairo blog peor o mejor no es que
n't get along with him you
no me llevo con él
understand but it doesn't mean that
me entendéis pero no quiere decir que a
those who haven't invited
los que no hayan invitado
are worse because in fact there are
sean peores porque es que de hecho hay
people who haven't invited who have
gente a la que no han invitado que tiene
more numbers more successes than some
más números más éxitos que algunas
people who are inside golan
personas que están dentro de golán
hegolan it is a server that he has created
hegolan es un servidor que él ha creado
the fbi with blondes and they have invited the
al fbi con rubios y han invitado a la
people they get along with but and
gente con la que se llevan bien pero y
now it's him but the hair of what I had to
ahora es él pero el pelo de lo que tenía
comment there
que comentar
are people invited by influence and there are
hay gente invitada por enchufe y hay
people who don't like each other that's why they
gente que entre ellos no se caen bien
had to do like
por eso tenían que hacer como ha hecho
wild has done and like vegeta has done this stack there
wild y como ha hecho vegeta está stack
is going to be controversy there is going to be there me
va a haber polémica va a haber ahí yo
who does not get involved I do
que no me meto
not get involved
no me meto
because willy rey ​​has put us in  because he doesn't
porque nos ha metido willy rey porque no
feel like it because he's there because he's stacked
le apetece porque está porque está stack
and at the slightest controversy and
y a la mínima que haya una polémica y se
that he's going to get hooked people avoid it
eso se va a enganchar pueblo evita
because he has no need controversy and such there are
porque no tiene necesidad polémica y tal
people there who sign up for the
hay gente ahí que se apunta por el
fake and the cohep Olympus because one thing
falseo y el cohep olimpo porque una cosa
that's going to have a lot of numbers a lot of
que va a tener muchos números mucho
success almost everyone and tries to kill
éxito casi todo el mundo e intenta matar
Aura Walt Rubios I mean if you see the
a aura walt rubios o sea si veis el
server everything pays for Aura or Rubio
servidor todo paga por aura o por rubio
okay Alvaro everything thank you very much why do
vale álvaro todo muchas gracias porque
n't they all go to kill Forward
no van todos a matar a delantero
Reach Members which is the same as a
alcance miembros que es igual a un
gum greetings totally totally
chicle saludos totalmente totalmente
why don't they all go to kill Cheto
porque no van todos a matar a cheto
no not everyone for Aurum Play or
no no todo el mundo por aurum play o por
Rubios to then make a video I eat
rubios para luego hacer un vídeo me como
Aurum Play euros kills me god
aurum play euros me mata dios
what's going on there are people who in
qué es lo que pasa que son gente que en
reality and everything said many times
realidad y todo dicho muchas veces
the tops among them are not friends
los tops entre ellos no son amigos
some and it takes away from us that some are
algunos y nos quita que algunos sean
friends one more friend of Perez and he's been with us
amigos a uno más amigo de pérez y está
all his life before becoming
de toda la vida de antes de hacerse
famous well before being famous not
famoso bueno antes de ser famoso no de
before YouTube but from when he had
antes de youtube pero de cuando tenía
many less numbers okay but there are
muchos menos números vale pero hay
some there that get along well because of fal
algunos allí que se llevan bien por fal
serious and eats for ism
serio y come por ismo
for numbers for collaborations and the
por números por colaboraciones y las
bases I would like the night the blond and
bases quisiera la noche el rubio y
Greece are truly false they are good that
grecia en verdad son falsas son bien que
we gave they are good that we gave the things that
dimos son bien que dimos las cosas que
the blond said in his live that if this one
dijo el rubio en su directo que si éste
comes for me for visits that if this one
viene por mí por visitas que si éste
comes for me and has the ego bush uploaded
viene por mí y tiene el ego bush subió
those things you think about them what happens is that
esas cosas las piensas lo que pasa que
in a moment of heat he has released them
en un momento de calentón las ha soltado
but when he already remembers a comment
pero cuando él ya recuerda un comentario
from another day it is because he has
de otro día es porque eso lo tiene
internalized that you understand as is that
interiorizado entendéis
then there is no come
tal cual que luego hay no venga las
pass them if the server is for good vibes I do
pases si el servidor es para buen rollo
n't know how it makes me feel good that I resign whatever you
no sé cómo me pone bien que dimito lo
want you can't see Saudis
que querais no se pueden ver saudíes
welcome
bienvenidos
but everything yesterday on twitter I saw the fund on
pero todo ayer en twitter vi los fund on
both blond and serious fighting I am
tanto de rubios y de grave pelear yo
welcome it is a [ __ ] madness I
bienvenido sea una [__] locura me
[ __ ] in the area anyway to comment a
cago en la zona en fin para comentar un
little what happened in fact we are going to
poco qué es lo que pasó de hecho vamos a
react to one of the videos okay in
reaccionar a uno de los vídeos vale de
fact here look writing recommended
hecho aquí mira escribiendo recomendado
50 minutes ago grave has uploaded a
hace 50 minutos de grave ha subido un
video and in the thumbnail it says
vídeo y en la miniatura pone
in the youtube photo
en la foto de youtube
of blond and black in millions of videos
de rubio y negro en millones de vídeos
on the platform and about  of this and some
en la plataforma y acerca de esto y unas
thumbnails that the [ __ ] mother who
miniaturas que la [__] madre que me
gave birth to me very inciting the salsa and
parió muy incitando al salsero y
literally what needs to be done is that I
literalmente lo que hay que hacer es que
already said it yesterday in the live and why
ya lo dije ayer en el directos y por qué
not upload the video yet always finish
no subir el vídeo todavía acabe siempre
the band I'm already inciting the sanse or
la banda ya voy incitando al sanse o
wait wait wait wait wait what
espera espérate espérate espérate que
wait to have a user we want this
espera tener usuario queremos que esto
golan which is the host an
de golán que es la [__] una serie
incredible series I think it is the most one of
increíble creo que es la más la una de
the best wonders that has been done in
la mejores maravillas que se ha hecho en
the community because this reminds me a
la comunidad porque esto me recuerda un
little bit of do you remember the forney tournament of
poco a acordáis del torneo de forney de
bringing together 100 people and there were a
juntar a 100 personas y que hubiera un
lot of moments in only two or
montón de momentos en solamente dos o
three hours like that but for weeks
tres horas así pero durante semanas
because it's going to be the form tournament and the
porque va a ser el torneo de forma y lo
same they invited colleagues okay and there were
mismo invitaron a colegas vale y había
invited people who don't even get along
gente invitada que ni siquiera se lleva
with the blond there were invited people who
con el rubio había gente invitada que
were invited through another
fueron invitadas a través de de otro
youtuber
youtuber
now it's on youtube it's not in denied it I do
ahora es en youtube no está en negó la
n't know if because they weren't invited because
no sé si porque no eran invitados porque
he didn't want that youtuber our denied
él no quería ese youtuber nuestra negó
it and that youtuber that they went through
la y eso youtuber que fueron a través de
security either why because they don't
seguridad tampoco por qué porque no
want to leave because in  the tournament the 22
quieren irnos porque en el torneo los 22
those youtubers so there's a lot of
ese youtubers o sea que hay mucho
nepotism buddy also
enchufismo compadre demás
a series that we want to last
una serie que queremos que dure rollos
weeks at least a month or something like that I do
semanas al menos un mes o algo así por
n't know exactly how long it's going to
el estilo no sé exactamente cuánto va a
last it depends on what people end up playing it
durar depende de lo que al final juegue
depends on what
la gente depende de lo que os gusta a
you like and of course it depends on how
vosotros y por supuesto depende de cómo
you behave because I literally think
os comportáis porque literalmente creo
that the fandom here is quite
que el fandom aquí es bastante
important to prevent the
importante para evitar que los propios
youtubers themselves from let's say scratching their
youtubers se digamos se rayan de su
own people in their own chat etc I'm
propia gente de su propio chat etc os
going to give you a personal example of mine okay
voy a poner un ejemplo mío personal vale
the other day I killed a play I said it in
el otro día maté a un play lo dije en el
yesterday's video that I uploaded mate aurum
vídeo de ayer de que subí mate aurum
play and it had the best endless and people
play y tenía lo mejor sin fin y personas
live and welcome so to have 25
en directo y bienvenidos así a tener 25
thousand because 10,000 people came from
mil porque vinieron 10.000 personas de
the aurum play streaming which is
el streaming de aurum play que es
completely normal because they will want to see
completamente normal porque querrán ver
and everything welcome thank you very much
y todo bienvenido a muchas gracias
who hasn't killed a play n in the
quien no ha matado a un play n en el
Russian who hasn't killed a play in the
ruso quien no ha matado a un play en el
Russian come see who was watching us around
ruso venga a ver quién nos miraba por
here aurum place ebola
aquí aurum place ébola
game play they
game play
killed him plate
le mataron plate
but  I want to see less summarized youtube videos
pero quiero ver vídeos de youtube menos
of these shitty ones, I wasn't
resumidas de estas de [__] no
going to euro play
ibai euro play
rb hadron play
rb hadron play
paul agon puts I open a play everyone
paul agon pone abro un play todos los
looks at
mira
another photo another one of everything a play is nice
otra foto otro de todo un play es bonito
now a play eats me
ahora un play me come
and surely if I go to other channels this is that
y seguro que si me voy a otros canales
I get a lot of garbage
es que esto me sale un montón de basura
man people summarized that [ __ ] [ __ ]
tío la gente resumido esas [__] [__]
basically what I want to say they have
básicamente lo que quiero decir han
done that everyone goes to put
hecho que van todo el mundo a ponerlo
employment for blonde to then make a
empleo por rubio para luego hacerse un
title of a thumbnail that is [ __ ]
título de una miniatura que está de [__]
great it is very good me to see you that I am
madre está muy bien yo ver a tú que yo
going to put a play in the thumbnail
voy a poner a un play en la miniatura
too but it's that my channel is salt I
también pero es que mi canal es de sal
know or then yours no maybe they don't
se o luego el vuestro no a lo mejor no
know the person who has killed a
conocen a la persona que ha matado a un
play I suppose and that break my face and
play supongo y que romperme la cara y
that it was for looking to see how he
que era por mirar a ver como él me
writes to me etcetera etcetera that seems
escriben etcétera etcétera eso me parece
[ __ ] great to me in fact it is super good
de [__] madre de hecho es súper bueno
because it's cool that there is a bubble of
porque mola que hay una burbuja de
strippers and youtubers that we are like 80
strippers y youtubers que seamos como 80
or so where we are
o así donde estamos colaborando
constantly collaborating to me that does not seem bad to me
constantemente a mí eso no me parece mal
what does seem bad to me obviously is
lo que sí me parece mal evidentemente es
seeing that they come  10,000 people and
ver que vienen 10.000 personas y a lo
maybe 500 or 1,000 people out of those 10,000
mejor 500 o mil personas de esas 10.000
people come and insult me,
personas pues vengan a insultar eso
obviously I think it's ugly, I've
evidentemente creo que está feo yo lo he
said it and I always say it in a way you can
dicho y siempre lo digo de manera dejas
literally eat my dick because you can
literalmente porque me podéis comer los
literally eat my balls because it's not going to get on my
huevos literalmente porque es de sacar
nerves at any time but maybe it does
de quicio ningún momento pero a lo mejor
n't get on my nerves but you
a mí no me saca de quicio pero sí que
can go to another youtuber who is a little
podéis ir a otro youtuber que es un poco
smaller who has I don't know in less
más pequeño que tiene no sé en menos
that he jumps less than me and you can even
que salta menos que yo y podéis incluso
get to scratch I read what happened here in
llegar a rayar leo lo que pasó aquí en
this case with the play review issue and
este caso con el tema de revisión play y
Louis and you think that they have nothing to do with what I
louis y crees que no tienen que ver a lo
'm saying but that it does have to
que estoy diciendo pero que sí que tiene
do with the fact that a lot of
que ver en cuanto a que fue un montón de
people went to Greg's chat to insult
gente al chat de greg para insultar el
Grave's chat went to the Rubios chat to
chat de grave fue al chat de rubios a
insult and in the end that is a [ __ ]
insultar y al final eso es una [__]
[ __ ] because we are all
[__] porque todos somos seres
human beings and we are all watching a
humanos y todos estamos viendo una
suitcase it would be normal and ordinary and if it
maleta sería normal y corriente y que si
goes to a video game it would be the kids from the
va a un videojuego sea los chavales del
Perez chat that is this  this is the skirt
chat pérez que está esto es el faldón
that we have this toxic fandom that
que tenemos a este el fandom tóxico que
you have okay, I hope I don't have
tenéis vale ya yo espero no tener
followers like that, really, they are followers
seguidores así de verdad sean seguidores
that I'm playing a video game with
que yo esté jugando un videojuego con
another and because I kill myself they go en masse to
otro y porque me mate vayan en masa a
insult me
insultar
for a video game, I mean, if you tell me
por un videojuego o sea si me dices a lo
maybe that the other youtube has
mejor que el otro youtube me ha
slandered me, that he has slandered me or that he has
calumniado que me ha calumniado o que me
done something very serious to me, well I understand a
ha hecho algo gravísimo pues entiendo un
little that neither because in the end I have to
poco que tampoco por al final que me
defend myself, it's me, I'll
tengo que defender soy yo ya me las
manage. I would never ask in fact if I see
apañaré yo nunca pediría de hecho si veo
that you enjoy people, I always usually gather together,
que disfrutáis a gente siempre suelo
okay,
reunir vale
you guys enjoy the spectacle and
ustedes disfrutar del espectáculo y
even okay, but
hasta vale pero
for a video game, I mean, for a
por un videojuego o sea por un
video game seriously, let's
videojuego en serio
see what happened was the following: I'm going to give
a ver lo que pasó fue lo siguiente le
my opinion, I'm going to give my
voy a dar mi opinión voy a dar mi
absolutely objective opinion, there
opinión absolutamente objetiva
being a click that will be uploaded to
habiendo un clic que estará subido a
youtube okay and they put a [ __ ]
youtube vale y le ponen a una [__] marca
watermark about all this and then I'm going
de agua acerca de todo esto y luego voy
to say what happens
a poner que lo que es lo que pasa
after the fight, okay, what happens,
después de la pelea vale lo que pasa
put okay, let's see, not exactly, let's
puesto vale vamos a ver no exactamente a
see if I can see it okay, this is, this is, I
ver si puedo verlo vale esto es esto es
think, well, here ours is like this, I can
creo no pues aquí nuestro es así puedo
see it really, no, it's not here, it's not
verlo realmente no aquí no está que no
where is it
está donde está
when they kill him exactly let's see what to
cuando le maten exactamente a ver de qué
think I'm from the ads uncle
pensar yo estoy de los anuncios tío
fire the please the youtube premium yes I
fuego la por favor el youtube premium sí
have youtube premium but that I don't
que tengo youtube premium pero que no
have in the background I don't have to
tengo en el grito de fondo no tengo a
see
ver
but it's not here exactly it's not here
pero no está aquí exactamente no está
the fight
aquí la pelea
not here this only after open your eyes this
no aquí esto sólo después abre los ojos
profile
está que perfil
the blond feel here it's not here that
el rubio sentirte aquí no está aquí esa
real part I had said a number
parte real había dicho yo una cantidad
of group everything that mother today the million
de grupo todo lo que madre hoy el millón
the best has also uploaded videos about
el mejor también ha subido videos sobre
fact I'm going to be the last today I'm not
hecho voy a ser el último hoy no soy yo
the king because my video is going to be the best
el rey porque mi vídeo va a ser el mejor
and I [ __ ] on the [ __ ] crazy maybe it
y me cago en la [__] loco a lo mejor
's falling here yes here yes it is
está cayendo aquí sí aquí sí que está
here yes it is this is that what happened
aquí sí que está esto es eso lo que pasó
okay they kept killing rubio antonio
vale no paraban de matar a rubio antonio
what's up dude how are you
que pasa churra cómo estás
a hug handsome thanks for becoming a
un abrazo guapo gracias por hacerte
member it seems like it or something there's
miembro es por lo que parece o tal hay
a rule the server that means
una norma el servidor que significa
bird flu means you can't go
gripe aviar significa que no puedes ir a
break a base and break it again and
romper una base y volver a romperla y
break it again and when they're
volver a romperla y ya cuando se están
giving up go and kill them with bullets wins all
rindiendo ir y matarlos a bala gana todo
the time well no that's bad it's ugly
el rato pues no eso está mal está feo
rust is not flu to rus it's  from the root of
rust no es de gripe a rus es de raíz de
arra and from ares make up a
arra y de ares montarte un plan de la
[ __ ] plan go to a base break the base to
[__] ir a una base romper la base en
steal things and say that's it,
robar las cosas y decir ya está hasta
we've reached our limit and when they recover
aquí hemos llegado y cuando se recuperen
then they won't go again or go for days
pues no volverá a ir o ir a los días
okay you can't go every day or all
vale no puedes ir todos los días o todo
the time to try things because
el rato a intentarlo en las cosas porque
as soon as they are literally
a la mínima que se están literalmente
recovering go back as if you are
recuperando volver a ir como como tú
stronger because he just
estás más fuerte porque él acaba de
stole all the things that he can go back
robar todas las cosas que puede volver
thanks after stealing
atrás gracias tras robar
that is literally almost and you are like
eso es literalmente casi y eres como
bullying practically and that is not done
bullying prácticamente y eso no se hace
on the server and that seems to be what
en el servidor y eso es parece lo que
happened it was already scratched in itself because I
pasó estaba rayado ya de por sí porque
posted a tweet that he had his cat to his
puse un tweet de que tenía su gata a su
cat that is sick so well in itself it
gato que está malito entonces pues ya de
is maybe something of the cattle or
por sí está a lo mejor algo del ganado o
depressed and then on top of that they were
decaído y luego encima que le estaban
killing it all the time and then what happens happens
matado todo el rato y luego pasa lo que
there are some rules for the flu there are some
pasa hay unas normas de gripe hay unas
rules here rubio is pretending to be the
normas aquí rubio se está haciendo de
administrator explaining that there are some
administrador explicando que hay unas
[ __ ] rules and it makes me very sad about the
[__] normas y a mí me da mucha pena que
noises the truth is I am serious that he
ruidos la verdad lo digo en serio que
is explaining in good faith we know that
está explicando de buena fe sabemos que
now we can do it is jimena  and I recorded
ya podemos hacer es jimena y los grabó
the stream LP it can be done because
el stream lp se puede hacer porque
you have a server rule if against
tienes una regla del servidor si contra
this email because in the end it would be cool not to
este email porque al final molaría no
stream but I was passing by to
hacer streaming pero se me pasaba a
give you my happy kings you are the best
darte mi feliz reyes eres el mejor
critical youtuber in the world man thanks
youtuber crítico del mundo hombre gracia
Antonio a hug
antonio un abrazo
here we also love you very much you already
aquí también te queremos mucho ya lo
know
sabe
for the chat because the chat is
para el chat porque el chat nos va a
always going to tell us all the [ __ ] time where it is
decir siempre todo el [__] rato el donde
people are always going to say
está la gente siempre va a decir
so to avoid that [ __ ] and
entonces para evitar esas [__] y
headaches look you can
dolores de cabeza mira se puede el
stream but the good thing would be if there
streaming pero lo bueno sería que no
was no streaming but we do this for
hubiera streaming pero esto hacemos por
you literally but it will go for one
vosotros literalmente pero irá por una
person all the time when you have already
persona todo el rato cuando ya habéis
killed that [ __ ] flu or
matado esa cosida gripe o
and here happens what didn't have to in the
y aquí pasa lo que no tenía que el
past here happens what shouldn't have
pasado aquí pasa lo que no tenga que
happened well
haber pasado
until it was he could have been see
pues hasta que fuera el pudo ser ver
how here here he gets heated he gets heated
como aquí aquí se calienta se calienta
Rubiales saying that about the [ __ ] server
rubiales diciendo eso del [__] server
etcetera etcetera
etcétera etcétera
then he starts to go with his things that are
luego ya empieza a ir con sus cosas que
said in heat okay there is no I
se dicen en caliente vale que no hay
think we shouldn't take it into account and
creo que no hay que tenerlo en cuenta y
David has come neither what he says nor Rubios
ha venido david ni lo que diga ni rubios
nor wanted it varies welcome towards the
ni lo quería varía bienvenida hacia el
serious I don't know if you have said he is leaving  taking into
grave no sé si habéis dicho se va habida
account the based because it is being seen
cuenta la basado porque se está viendo
from the camera the blonde the blonde is going to
desde la cámara el rubio el rubio va a
talk to them today the kid 'stop since I'm
hablar con ellos hoy el chaval 'para ya
not having a good time you know
que no me lo estoy pasando bien sabe
put everything supports the measure of played the
mete todo apoya la medida de jugado el
time killing me is that in the end I am
tiempo matándome es que al final me está
getting a string and [ __ ] and no
saliendo un string y una [__] y no
but my experience with another being
pero mi experiencia con otra siendo
good and with the serious pass the funny one
buena y con el grave pase el graciosito
in front of his entire audience and when
delante de todo su audiencia y cuando
the blonde is talking so that there would not
está el rubio hablando para que no
be this pin but we do this
hubiera este pin pero esto lo hacemos
for you literally
por vosotros literalmente
but go for a person all the time
pero ir a por una persona todo el rato
when you have already killed that [ __ ]
cuando ya le habéis matado esa cosida
flu or
gripe o
and here happens
y aquí pasa lo que no tiene que el
what does not have to be the past here happens what does not have to be past because until it was he could be see the same here here it gets heated it gets heated blondes saying that about the [ __ ] server etcetera etcetera then things start things that are said in the heat of the moment okay no no I don't
dicen en caliente vale que no que no hay
think that we should not take it into account
creo que no hay que tenerlo en cuenta
obviously neither what blondes say nor
obviamente ni lo que diga ni rubios ni
what I say maybe when raid kills me
lo que diga yo a lo mejor cuando me mata
for example that the best I say things
raid por ejemplo que lo mejor digo cosas
in the heat of the moment etc. what I say what I
en caliente etc lo que yo digo lo que yo
say to him for example rich when he kills me well it
le digo por ejemplo rich cuando me mata
is  that pisses me off it pisses me off but
pues es que me cabrea me cabrea pero a
maybe I'm like let's say I'm not
lo mejor estoy como digamos no le ando
in quotes you know how I am
entre comillas ya sabéis cómo soy yo
but here the noise thing I think is not
pero aquí lo de ruidos creo que no es
role-playing or what will really get them done
rol o sea que lo que les acabará de
okay and it's normal that he goes down and doesn't
verdad vale y es normal que baja y no le
say things to him he's pissed off for the ball he
dice cosas cabrera por el huevo se le
says things to him that he has to internalize he
dice cosas que las tiene interiorizar
's only totally naked look he's
sólo está totalmente desnudo mira está
naked he's in shot since I don't want
desnudo está en plano ya que no quiero
anything to happen and suddenly well he
que pase nada y de repente pues bien
thanks and gets up well for him ha ha
agradece y levanta pues por el ja ja
here rubios I agreed with rubios
aquí rubios yo le di la razón a rubios
that it was done badly okay it's
de que está mal hecho vale está bastante
done quite badly but everything I did after
mal hecho pero todo lo que hice después
rubios from outside to come back from the server I do
rubios de fuera ser regrese del server
n't know that that created a bad atmosphere that I
no sé que eso haya crea mal ambiente que
think is
creo que
good okay and that's why that's why and it's
está bien está bien y por eso por eso y
also very good on the part of rubio he
está también muy bien por parte de rubio
exposed this tweet ballet sorry for
expuso este tuit ballet sorry por
getting like that and leaving between that my cat
ponerme así e irme entre que mi gata
is sick okay and that she hasn't slept very
está malita vale y que no ha dormido muy
well today I'm a little older more and
bien hoy estoy un poco mayor a más y
better this tweet is very good and of
mejor está muy bien este tuit y por
course I think that later there will be a tweet
supuesto creo que después hay un tweet
from ruby ​​if you see it fails
de rubí si la ven falla
answering gref the surf has stolen
contestando a gref el surf me ha robado
my thumbnail about golán
mi miniatura sobre golán
seriously
serio
the gentleman
el señor
then the eggs you do not have to win what
entonces los huevos no tienes que ganar
this miniature
a esta miniatura
but I have seen it but I thought that
pero la he visto pero me creía que se la
Alexis Changos had stolen it
alexis changos
bird of
ave
course needing it also had it on
claro necesitando también la tenía
ah half the internet caught me that miniature
ah me cogió medio internet esa miniatura
then it is serious okay then he put this
luego está grave vale luego le puso este
okay I'm sorry if our way of playing
vale lo siento si nuestra forma de jugar
has been too aggressive in the end it is
ha sido demasiado agresiva al final es
a game and we have to stay with
un juego y nos tenemos que quedar con
the hours of entertainment that
las horas de entretenimiento que no
were not botox and from the outside bad vibes
estaban botox y de afuera mala vibra
outside is also okay this tweet the
fuera también está bien este tuit la
answer I'm sorry for having gotten heated and for having
contestación siento haberme calentado y
said ugly things about you etcetera etcetera
haber dicho cosas feas de ti etcétera
you know what happens here there is
etcétera sabes lo que pasa que aquí hay
a good vibe of the host okay a
un buen rollo de la de la [__] vale un
good vibe a sorry an okay and it's false
buen rollo un perdón un vale y es falso
well what an abyss for the camera and for the
bien que abismo para la cámara y para la
people okay everything goes well but then you
gente vale todo sale bien pero luego
keep reading down and it's on
sigues leyendo hacia abajo y está en
you dude you
vosotros tío vosotros
are literally poisoning something
qué estáis literalmente intoxicando algo
that is not there it has stayed here that's it
que no hay más se ha quedado aquí ya
guys it has stayed here and that's it
está chicos se ha quedado aquí y ya está
nothing happens nothing happens besides these
no pasa nada no pasa nada además estos
first days of the golan are the days of the
primeros días del golán son los días del
prologue because tomorrow Thursday they remove everything it
prólogo porque mañana jueves quitan todo
comes back the whole server resets and that's
vuelve se resetea todo el servidor y es
how the [ __ ] begins  seriously when
como ya empieza lo [__] serio cuando ya
the thing of making a house starts and
empieza el tema de hacerte una casa y
when they raid you is when it's going to
cuando ya te raiden es cuando ya te va a
really screw you then this is a little you
[__] de verdad entonces esto es un poco
leave from the game on it's going to be
dejas a partir del juego ya va a ser lo
truly serious and where you're really
verdaderamente serio y donde de verdad
going to see who is good who is bad
se va a ver quién es bueno quién es malo
and a lot of things now my opinion of
y un montón de cosas ahora mi opinión de
how it should be of golan in the end the
cómo debería serlo de golán al final la
series is not mine I participate I love to
serie no es mía yo participo me encanta
participate I
participar
had a great time with all the people
me lo pasé súper bien con toda la gente
in it
que hay dentro
and I would like there to be less killing the
y me gustaría que no se matara tanto la
truth is that it wasn't like a roll
verdad que no fuera en plan rollo
we meet at 8 on the mountain and we go
quedamos a las 8 en la montaña y vamos
with the best weapons if there is killing it would be
con las mejores armas si a matar hay
cool I would also charge some rum some I do
molaría también cobraba algo de ron algo
n't know wait for the wars a
de no sé esperar a que las guerras un
few more days because in the end we have
poco más de días porque al final
been three days in the golan and we have
llevamos tres días en el golán y tenemos
very good weapons here is the best weapon
muy buenas armas la acá es la mejor arma
in the game it is saved that there are no
del juego se guarda que no hay
helicopters but the helicopters
helicópteros pero los helicópteros
can be on day 4 on day 5 and
pueden estar en el día 4 en el día 5 y a
maybe we can get I don't know if to
lo mejor podemos llegar no sé si a
burn the series but I would not like it in
quemar la serie pero no me gustaría en
my opinion it is that I would not like
mi opinión es que no me gustaría que
things to be so fast and that  I would
fuera tan rápido las cosas y que se
burn through the series so fast I think that's
quemara la serie tan rápido creo que es
my opinion I maybe maybe I wouldn't put it
mi opinión yo quizá quizá no pondría
like I would put it the 8 hours on the
como la me pondría lo de 8 horas en el
server
servidor
you know if you're more than 8 hours
sabéis que si estás más de 8 horas
in the server they kick you out okay they
dentro el servidor te echan vale te
wanted to [ __ ] you okay [ __ ] you I
querían a tomar por culo vale a tomar
think I would even lower it
por culo yo creo que lo bajaría incluso
hop and how do you become a member from
hop y cómo te haces miembro desde
youtube I don't see how to do it next to
youtube no veo cómo hacerlo al lado de
the days next to thanks to you and
los días al lado gracias a ti y
Guillermo next to the
guillermo al lado del botón de
subscribe button next to it you have a button that
suscribirte al lado tienes un botón que
says join look here looked you see on the
pone unirse mira aquí mirado veis en el
folk channel I make a go
canal de folk hago un irme
so that everything would be a little slower
para que todo fuera un poquito más lento
so that in those four hours you would have
para que en esas cuatro horas te diera
time to farm and maybe a little more
tiempo a farmar y quizás un poco más de
shots for him but no no exaggerated and
disparos para él pero no no exagerado y
then we'll talk I talk okay my opinion is not worth a [ __ ] [ __ ] within the administration and within everything but I think it would be the best for you guys so that you can have more content and maybe more elaborate like
contenido y quizá más elaborado en plan
this because not surrounding you don't know what it
de esto porque no rodear no sabéis lo
is I don't talk I talk about that role like
que es no hablo hablo de que ese rol en
let's fix it with a bar it's going to be
plan vamos a arreglar con barra me va
radu no no no we're not going to plan  roll well
radu no no no vamos a plan rollo pues
that there is a story or that there is a little
que haya una historia o que haya un poco
more dialogue you know what would fly go that
más de diálogo sabéis lo que volaría ir
I was going ruby ​​use faucet
de que se iba yo rubí uso grifo
any any person who is there
cualquier cualquier persona que está ahí
meet with another person naked and say
quedar con otra persona desnuda y decir
let's see why you are not in exchange
vamos a ver por qué no estéis de cambio
because you know what to say in a
porque se sabe lo que decir en plan
roll plan that there is a dialogue that there is is what
rollo que haya un diálogo que haya es lo
I would like and I think I would do it
que me gustaría y creo que lo haría
much better in terms of the series but you
bastante mejor en cuanto a la serie pero
know that in the end this is not in my
ya sabéis que esto al final no en mi
series and you can do what is going to be
serie y se puede hacer lo que se va a
done for what is going to be done then there are
hacer por lo que se va a hacer luego
great then in the end I put a
haya grandes luego al final puso un
last tweet I have had a thousand live streams in which
último tweet he tenido mil directos en
I have gotten heated for a game and
los que me he calentado por un juego y
done ugly things I appreciate the tweet
hecho cosas feas te agradezco el tweet
we are people we all get the rush
somos personas a todos nos pasa el rush
it's a demon after the web if you want we stay playing
es un demonio después del web si querés
the trumpet you
quedamos tocando la trompeta
forgive each other and then well look
se perdonan y luego pues mira ya la
people should moderate themselves a little and do
gente debe a moderarse un poco y hacerte
self-criticism such that this is not bad at
autocrítica tal que esto no está mal del
all worth it because in the end it is
todo vale porque al final es una crítica
constructive criticism what people are into
constructiva en lo que está la gente
only the child is they create hate well
solo el niño es crean odio pues
possibly but I think that it is not only
posiblemente pero yo creo que no sólo
children there are people who have  hair
son los niños hay gente que tiene pelos
on the balls and also creates quite a
en los huevos y también crea bastante
lot of hate not only in him not only in
bastante odio no sólo en él no sólo en
the fans where big blond was not
los fan donde grande rubio no era
absolutely all and even in mine
absolutamente todos e incluso en el mío
because it is something uncontrollable there is a
porque es algo incontrolable hay un
small percentage at the end of the ard and a
pequeño porcentaje al final de la ard y
thousand people who came from the
mil personas que vinieron del streaming
aurum play streaming he would only insult me
de aurum play a mí sólo me insultara a
maybe I'm talking to you about 500 maybe it's not
lo mejor te hablo de 500 quizás no son
1500 and it's a small percentage even
1500 y es un pequeño porcentaje incluso
I assured that someone had been killed
yo aseguró que se había mata a alguien
surely the percentage of my people
seguro que el porcentaje de mi gente
too maybe
también a lo mejor
a hug javi they quote your videos
un abrazo javi me citan tus vídeos
funny fuss but I don't understand why
gracia alboroto pero no entiendo por qué
people go to someone else's chat and you
la gente va al chat de otro y tú de
insult me ​​I imagine that in media
insultar yo me imagino que en medios
like in a pig plan they
como en un plan cerdo
don't use half a half joke not
no se emplean medio medio cachondeo no
because there are people who really take
porque hay gente que realmente se toma a
a [ __ ] video game to heart
pecho un [__] videojuego
but I say I tell you about the subject between
pero digo ya os digo del tema entre el
ruby ​​​​really already had these things
rubí realmente ya llevaba estas cosas
that they do what he said is true he
que hagan que ha dicho es verdad las
had them inside that he doesn't say them in his
tenía dentro que no las diga en sus
live shows that he doesn't tica the face because you
directos que no la tica la cara porque
don't want the pse or because he doesn't want
no quieras al pse o porque no quiere
problem because he didn't need it is
problema porque no tenía necesidad es
something else but the things had to
otra cosa pero las cosas tenía
internalize those are things  that he
interiorizar esas son cosas que él
thinks this about him 3 he made a
piensa esto de él 3 me puso un
comment to me the other day it's already quite strange
comentario el otro día ya bastante raro
that we are high they always come to
que estamos subidito siempre vienen a
kill me, me for the visit these are things he
matarme a mí por la visita son cosas que
thinks he keeps quiet when he's
piensa que se las calla cuando está
angry of course but then
enfadado claro pero que luego las
we had a good time
pasábamos de buen rollo
this final are collaborations and such
esta final son colaboraciones y tal
rugby wants to be bad from chile
el rugby quiere estar mal del chile
passed also by towards the cape the
pasado también por hacia el cabo la
position of the blonde is not that of Greece
posición del rubio no es la de grecia
for the position of the blonde is that the
para la posición del rubio es que el el
ruby ​​​​no longer works because he needs the
rubí ya no trabaja porque necesita el
money and a salary
dinero y un sueldo
the blonde sweats his life now the blonde
el rubio se la suda la vida ya el rubio
can [ __ ] and not do anything else
puede [__] y no hacer más nada
ever again in his entire life and have it all
nunca más en toda su vida y tenerlo todo
Jupiter welcome the blonde does it now
júpiter bienvenidos el rubio lo hace ya
the things that follow the course he does them because he
las cosas que sigue el rumbo las hace
wants to do them because he likes it and
porque quiere hacerle porque le gusta y
the blonde does not feel like the nonsense he
al rubio no le apetece los mamoneos él
starts playing and sits here on the
se pone a jugar y se pone aquí en el
server to have a good time to play and
servidor a pasárselo bien a jugar ya
have a good experience and make a
tener una experiencia buena y hacer un
to be a fun string okay and if he
a ser un string divertido vale y si lo
has it as a serious job he has gone to
tiene como un trabajo grave se ha ido a
Andorra to stay with more money
andorra para quedarse con más dinero
possible than if he were here in Spain
posible que si estuviera aquí en españa
to take advantage of the time that lasts  The thing
para aprovechar la época que le dure lo
about YouTube for work is fine, and
de youtube para trabajar vale y el
rugby is not the same, okay, so he's not
rugbier no es lo mismo vale entonces no
looking for content or looking to have a
va buscando contenido o buscando
good time, okay, and the other one is living with
pasárselo bien vale y el otro está viví
Pib and with him he's next to him, pi pi pi pi pi, it's
pib y con él está al lado pi pi pi pi pi
been funny in what there is.
ha sido ser gracioso en lo que hay